Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - GSS (1), 03/14/1983; gss_303; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Slates: 101, 103, 105: "Let magician shapes this world" (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 03/14/1983; gss_304; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 24)
    Content cont'd from 303: Slates: 201-209: "LEt magician shapes this world" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 210: Magnificant (Latin) (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (3), 03/14/1983; gss_305; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Content cont'd from 304: Slates: 301-314: Magnificat (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (4), 03/14/1983; gss_306; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Slates: 401-405: (?) (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 406-407: "Gloria..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 408: "Amen..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 409: "Gloria..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 410: "O..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 411 (?) (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 412: "O..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (5), 03/14/1983; gss_307; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Contd from 306: Slates: 501: "O..." (choruses mixed, unaccomp.); 502: (?) (men's chorus, unaccomp.); 503-508: "Fe Chi...." (women's chorus, unaccomp.); 509-510: "E..." (women's chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (1), 04/03/1983; gss_890; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - GSS (1), 04/08/1983; gss_068; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Come Along Expected Jesus", mixed chorus, unaccompanied."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (2) (from 205), 04/08/1983; gss_069; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Continued from gss_068: "Come Along Expected Jesus" (Jim is asked for his thoughts). Soprano solo with male chorus, unaccompanied".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (3), 04/08/1983; gss_070; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Mixed chorus "2 measurer"; Women's chorus, different music".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (4) (to 409), 04/08/1983; gss_071; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Women's chorus. (asks Bill for his thoughts). Men's chorus unaccompanied. Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (5), 04/08/1983; gss_072; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (6), 04/08/1983; gss_073; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (7), 04/08/1983; gss_074; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Glory Be to God", mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (8), 04/08/1983; 04/11/1983; gss_075; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Glory Be to God", mixed chorus; piano, soprano solo; "Ave Maria", mixed chorus."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (9), 04/11/1983; gss_076; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Ave Maria", mixed chorus"; "Solve Regina"."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (10), 04/11/1983; gss_077; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (11), 04/11/1983; gss_078; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Mixed chorus, unaccompanied".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 6)
  - GSS (12), 04/11/1983; gss_079; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (13), 04/11/1983; gss_080; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (14), 04/11/1983; gss_081; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (15), 04/11/1983; gss_082; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Ever afterward refuse" (men chorus)."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (1), 05/03/1983; gss_083; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (2), 05/03/1983; gss_084; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Serenata....", mixed chorus; Sukiyaki".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (3), 05/03/1983; gss_085; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "mixed chorus".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 7)
  - GSS (1), 11/21/1983; gss_308; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Slates: 101: "See the rainbow..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 102-104: "See the rainbow..." (mixed chorus, tenor, unaccomp.); 105; 106-107: "Dawn..." (mixed chorus, tenor, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (2), 11/21/1983; gss_309; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Slates: 201-207: ".... across the sky..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 208: "I am haunted by the ...." (soprano solo; baritone, oboe, flute clarinet)
  - GSS (3), 11/21/1983; gss_310; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Cont'd from 309: Slates: 301-304: "I am haunted ..." (different measurer on some slates); 305-311: "I am haunted ..." (mixed choruses, soprano solo, oboe flute, etc.)
  - GSS (4), 11/21/1983; gss_311; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Cont'd from 310: Slates: 401-404: "Into the hollow of my soul..." (mixed chorus, oboe, etc.); 405-410: "No one ..." (mixed chorus, oboe, soprano solo, sound effects); 411: -412: "I am haunted..." (mixed chorus, oboe, soprano solo, sound effects); 413: ? (mixed chorus, oboe, soprano solo, sound effects); 414: 2 notes on oboe
  - GSS (5), 11/21/1983; gss_312; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 25)
    Slates: 501-504: "See the rainbow" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (1), 01/16/1984; gss_139; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Daryl mentioned, tenor, soprano, bass".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - GSS (2), 01/16/1984; gss_140; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Daryl mentioned, questioned, tenor, soprano, mixed".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - GSS (3), 01/16/1984; gss_141; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Daryl mentioned, baritones, basses, tenors, soprano, altos, baritones, basses".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - GSS (4), 01/16/1984; gss_142; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Soprano, alto, tenor, bass, baritone. Discuss clothing, driving, etc.".; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - GSS (1), 02/19/1984; gss_491; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    101-109: (chorus)
  - GSS (2), 02/19/1984; gss_492; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd from 491: 201-209: (chorus)
  - GSS (3), 02/19/1984; gss_493; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd from 492: 301-307: "His body was..." (chorus); 308: "My ..." (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 02/19/1984; gss_494; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd from 493: 401-408: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (5), 02/19/1984; gss_495; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    Contd from 494: 501-505: (chorus)
  - GSS (6), 02/19/1984; gss_496; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 39)
    601-609: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (1), 02/20/1984; gss_497; Recording of chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    101-105: "The Philosopher Diogenes" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (2), 02/20/1984; gss_498; Recording of chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd from 497: 201-210: "The Philosopher Diogenes" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (3), 02/20/1984; gss_499; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd from 498: 301-306: "The Philosopher Diogenes" - "Country Fair" (chorus); 307: "The Philosopher Diogenes" - "Honest man" (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 02/20/1984; gss_500; Recording of chorus performance without accompaniment. Gregg Smith talks about phonograph needle and compact disc (when it comes).; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd from 499: 401-405: "The Philosopher Diogenes" - "Honest man" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (5), 02/20/1984; gss_501; Recording of chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    503-512: "Cats, cats, and more cats" (chorus, unaccomp.); 513: "Cat in the winter window" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (6), 02/20/1984; gss_502; Recording of chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    601-602: "Cat in the winter window" (chorus, unaccomp.); 603-604:"She yawns" (chorus); 605-615: "I walk down the street with my dinosaur" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (1), 11/12/1984; gss_503; Recording of mixed chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    101-107: "Early to bed and early to rise" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 108-111: "He that goes a borrowing..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (2), 11/12/1984; gss_504; Recording of mixed chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd. from 503: 201-202: "He that goes a borrowing, goes a sorrowing..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 203-211: "Look before you leap" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 212-213: "All that gl. Hers isn't gold..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (3), 11/12/1984; gss_505; Recording of mixed chorus performance without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd. from 504: 301: "Forever" (chorus); 302: "All that gl. Hers isn't gold" (chorus); 303: "Never judge a book by its cover" (chorus); 304: "A thing of beauty is a joy forever" (chorus); 305-308: "Make haste, slowly haste" (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 11/12/1984; gss_506; Recording of chorus performance with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd. from 505: 401: "Leasure [sic]"; 402-404: "Make haste, slowly haste..."; 405-415: (chorus, Roz)
  - GSS (5), 11/12/1984; gss_507; Recording of chorus and soprano performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 40)
    Contd. from 506: 501-503/505-507/509: (chorus, Roz)
  - GSS (6), 11/12/1984; gss_508; Recording of chorus and soprano performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    601-603: (soprano Roz, chorus)
  - GSS (1), 11/13/1984; gss_509; Recording of chorus and soprano performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    101-114: (soprano, chorus)
  - GSS (2), 11/13/1984; gss_510; Recording of male and mixed chorus performances with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 509: 201-203: (male chorus); 204-213: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (3), 11/13/1984; gss_511; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 510: 301-310: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (4), 11/13/1984; gss_512; Recording of mixed chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 41)
    Contd. from 511: 401-402: (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (1), 02/18/1985; gss_020; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (2), 02/18/1985; gss_704; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (3), 02/18/1985; gss_705; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (4), 02/18/1985; gss_706; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (5), 02/18/1985; gss_707; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (6), 02/18/1985; gss_708; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (7), 02/18/1985; gss_709; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (8), 02/18/1985; gss_710; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (1), 05/13/1985; gss_205; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    101-104: "I Am The Rose of Sharon..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 105: (altos, sopranos, tenors, baritones, unaccomp., mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 05/13/1985; gss_206; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    201-205: (Latin text) (soprano, altos, tenors, baritones, bases); 206: (German text) (piano accomp., baritone, "Schubert song Cycle" [?] (choir added, tenor)
  - GSS (3), 05/13/1985; gss_207; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 15)
    301: (German leader) (baritone, piano); 302: (German leader) (baritone, piano, tenor added, chorus); 303: (German leader) (baritone, piano, tenor added, chorus); 304-305: "Buy, buy, buy..." (See what you want before you buy) (alto, mixed chorus - round form)
  - GSS (4), 05/13/1985; gss_208; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    401-403: "Buy, buy..." (soloists and choruses, unaccomp.); 404: talk; 405: "Gloria Deo...." (choruses, unaccomp.); 406: Latin [?] (piano, soprano, chorus)
  - GSS (5), 05/13/1985; gss_209; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    501-503 (piano, soprano, chorus); 504-508: "Hallelujah..." (piano, choruses)
  - GSS (6), 05/13/1985; gss_210; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    601: "Hallelujah..." (piano, choruses, soprano solo); 602: Latin (?) (piano, choruses, soprano solo); 603: (?) (piano, choruses, soprano solo, Car); 604: "Sorrow..." (piano, choruses, soprano solo)
  - GSS (7), 05/13/1985; gss_211; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    701-705: "Sorrow..." (piano, chorus, creaking floors, GS gets angry) 706: "Sparrows in the East (soprano solo, whispering) "Now Carmen"
  - GSS (8), 05/13/1985; gss_580; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (9), 05/13/1985; gss_212; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    901-902: "Sorrow" (piano, chorus); 903: "Sorrow" (piano, chorus, church bells, GS mixed dialogue); 904: "The Sorrow of Love" (choruses, piano); 905: (laugh)
  - GSS (10), 05/13/1985; 05/14/1985; gss_581; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (11), 05/14/1985; gss_582; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 43)
  - GSS (12), 05/14/1985; gss_213; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1201-1205: "Love Parade" (piano, choruses, some lyrics in French); 1206: (?) (choruses unaccomp.)
  - GSS (13), 05/14/1985; gss_214; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1501-1504: (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1505: "Praise"; 1506-1507: "Men call me thou" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1508-1517: (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1518: "Rest"; 1519: (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (14), 05/14/1985; gss_215; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1401: "Rest..." (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1402: (?) (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1403: "Joy at the uprising..." (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1404: "Behold ..." (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1405-1407 (?) (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1408: "Everlasting Day" (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1409: "Joy at the uprising" (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1410-1413: "Day..." (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.); 1414-1417: (?) (chorus, mixed, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (15), 05/14/1985; gss_216; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1501-1503: (?) (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1504: "We May See..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1505-1506: "Raise" (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1507-1509: "Salvation..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1509-1513: (?) (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (16), 05/14/1985; gss_217; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1601-1605: (?) (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1606: "The Night Was Made For Love" - popular song (mixed chorus, soprano, baritone solo duet, piano accomp., English, French lyrics)
  - GSS (17), 05/14/1985; gss_218; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 16)
    1701-1704: "The Night Was Made for Love" (mixed chorus, piano accomp., soprano baritone duet, solos, French English lyrics); 1705: "... Cloistered in thy ..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1706: "leaves this world below to...." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1707: ... Cloistered in thy ..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.); 1708 (?) (mixed chorus, unaccomp.);; 1709: "Come ..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (18), 05/14/1985; gss_219; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    1801-1816: mixed chorus, unaccomp.
  - GSS (19), 05/14/1985; gss_220; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    1901-1908: "By miracles..." (mixed chorus, no accomp.); 1909-1914: "Scribe of Father..." (mixed chorus, no accomp.)
  - GSS (20), 05/14/1985; gss_221; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    2001-2004: ? (mixed chorus, unaccomp., solo alto, soprano solo); 2005-2008: piano (Bach?) Partita (woman artist, soloist); 2009-2010: piano (same piece, different arrangement)
  - GSS (21), 05/15/1985; gss_222; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    2101-2107: piano (cont. from gss_221, same piece, channels 3 and 4 are closer to the piano); 2108-2112: "... smiles and rears..." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)2113: "I wish...." (mixed chorus, unaccomp.)
  - GSS (22), 05/15/1985; gss_223; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 17)
    2201-2203: "I wish..." (mixed chorus); 2204-2205: "Such Mercy..." (mixed chorus); 2205-2208: "Die ..." (mixed chorus); 2209-2210: "Murder..." (mixed chorus); 2211-2216: "What can be ..." (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (23), 05/15/1985; gss_021; Mixed chorus with piano; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - GSS (24), 05/15/1985; gss_700; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (25), 05/15/1985; gss_701; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (26), 05/15/1985; gss_702; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (27), 05/15/1985; gss_703; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 54)
  - GSS (1), 06/14/1985; gss_350; Recording of mixed chorus with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    101: "With this kind" Louise asked for opinion (mixed chorus); 102: "Joseph" (mixed chorus); 103-105: "Whit this kind" (mixed chorus);106-108: "Take thy.." (mixed chorus); 109-110: "The world..." (mixed chorus); 111/115-118: "Wince comes" (mixed chorus); 112-114: "The world..." (mixed chorus);119: "And all that should be writ..." (mixed chorus); 120: "A shadow seen..." (mixed chorus); 121-123: "but as far ..." (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (2), 06/14/1985; gss_351; Recording of chorus, tenors.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    201: Louise; 202: "Thos began..." (chorus); 203-206: (tenors and chorus); 207-210/219-221: "Fleshly..." (tenors and chorus); 211-218: (tenors and chorus); 222-223: "Row" (tenors and chorus);224-226: "Which was..." (tenors and chorus)
  - GSS (3), 06/14/1985; gss_352; Recording of chorus performance.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 31)
    301-321: (chorus); 321:"Loves..." (chorus); 322-323: "doors..." (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 06/14/1985; gss_313; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    401-402/303-304: "Let me..." (women's chorus); 400/405-411: "With the key..." (men's chorus); 412: "Unlock the locks..." (men's chorus); 413-421: "Saffolk the doors" (mixed chorus); 422: "Pledge" (mixed chorus); 423-425: "Oh La" (mixed chorus); 426-429: "Dearest come" (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (5), 06/14/1985; gss_314; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    501-504: "... walk up" (chorus); 505-511: "Oh So..." and "Walk up" (chorus); 512: "No ma" (chorus); 513-520: "I know..." "Region" (chorus); 522-523: "Always" (chorus)
  - GSS (6), 06/14/1985; gss_315; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    601-603: "... always in that region" (chorus); 604: "Region..." (chorus); 606-609/612-613: "Come, come, come" (chorus); 610-611: "Aunt Susan" (chorus); 614: "Lea" (chorus); 615: "Dins death" (chorus); 616: "Undulate" (chorus)
  - GSS (1), 10/15/1985; gss_316; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    101-111/113-114: "I lift my eyes ..." (chorus, some German lyrics, tenor); 112: "I lift my eyes ..." (chorus, some German lyrics, tenor); 115: "the mountain tops ..." (piano, soprano solo, chorus)
  - GSS (2), 10/15/1985; gss_317; Recordings with piano, soprano, chorus, bass, tenor solos, with comments.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    201: "Everlasting spring ..." (piano, soprano, chorus, Bill again asked to comment); 202-203: ? (piano, soprano, chorus); 204-216: "Sing-a-ling" (soprano, bass, tenor solos)
  - GSS (3), 10/15/1985; gss_318; Recordings with chorus, soprano solo, baritone, bass solos, accapella, tenor, discussions.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    301-309: "Cities that start with S" (chorus, soprano solo, baritone, bass solos, accapella, Bill is asked his opinion); 310-312: "Sing-a-long" (chorus, soprano solo, baritone, bass solos); 313-314: "Sing-a-long" (chorus, tenor); 315-322: "... Walk up, walk up" (chorus)
  - GSS (4), 10/15/1985; gss_319; Recordings with unaccompanied chorus, soprano solo with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    401-403: " Walk up, walk up..." (chorus, unacomp.); 404-409: "I know..." (chorus, unacomp.); 410-414: "When he did see ..." (piano accomp., soprano solo); 415-421: (Naomi in German and tenor)
  - GSS (5), 10/15/1985; gss_320; Recording of chorus and various artists, some sing in German.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    501-514: (tenor in German, piano); 515: (chorus); 516-520: "O, Billy, O" (unaccomp., tenor solo, soprano solo, baritone solo)
  - GSS (6), 10/15/1985; gss_321; Recording of chorus, tenor and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    601: "O, Billy, O" (chorus); 602-609: "O, Billy, O" (chorus and tenor); 610-618: "O, Billy, O" (chorus, tenor and soprano)
  - GSS (7), 10/15/1985; gss_322; Recording of chorus, soprano and tenor.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    701-705: "O, Billy, O" sung as a sound (chorus soprano and tenor); 706-708: "I remember sky and days" (soprano solo, piano accomp., chorus)
  - GSS (8), 10/15/1985; gss_323; Recording with soprano solo, piano, chorus, talks about the weather and next day activities.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 28)
    801-804: "I remember sky and days" (soprano, piano, chorus); 805: (tenor, soprano, other interplay)
  - GSS (1); [Louise] Talma: Wreath (start), 11/14/1985; gss_577; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (2); [Louise] Talma: Wreath (cont.), 11/14/1985; gss_578; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (3), 11/14/1985; gss_579; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 46)
  - GSS (4), 11/14/1985; gss_566; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (5), 11/14/1985; 11/15/1985; gss_567; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (6), 11/15/1985; gss_568; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 45)
  - GSS (2), 01/08/1986; gss_346; Recording of mixed choruses.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    201: "Poverty..." (mixed chorus, percussion, same phrases); 202-205: "destitution..." (mixed chorus, percussion, same phrases, soprano); 206-216: (mixed choruses)
  - GSS (3), 01/08/1986; gss_347; Recording of mixed choruses.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    Cont'd from 346: 301-320: (mixed choruses)
  - GSS (4), 01/08/1986; gss_348; Recording of chorus with piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    401-417: (chorus, piano)
  - GSS (5), 01/08/1986; gss_349; Recording of chorus performance with piano accompaniment, discussions and conversation at the end.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    Cont'd from 348: 501: "Slow, slow..." "Sheep..." "Hills, hills", Bob is asked his opinion (piano, chorus)
  - GSS (1), 05/07/1986; gss_338; Recording of various songs in English and German with tenor, bass, choir, with or without piano accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    101: "Declaration of Independence" "Friendship" in German and English (piano, tenor, bass, choir); 106-120 (choir)
  - GSS (2), 05/07/1986; gss_339; Recording of chorus performances with discussion and comments by Gregg Smith.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    201-206: (chorus); 207-223: (chorus, alto and soprano, with piano accompaniment)
  - GSS (3), 05/07/1986; gss_340; Recording of chorus, soprano performance with and without accompaniment.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    311: ? (fragment); 309-313: "Woman of the world"(chorus, piano, soprano, waltz time); 301: "Beautiful she was" (chorus, piano, soprano, waltz time); 302-304: "Beautiful false teeth" (chorus, piano, soprano, waltz time); 305: ?; 314-320: "Sing Hosanna" (chorus, soprano)
  - GSS (4), 05/07/1986; gss_341; Recording of chorus unaccompanied and with piano accompaniment, tenor, baritone and soprano.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    401-405: "Sing Hosanna" (chorus, unaccomp.); 406-424: "How come everybody talks about the weather" (chorus, piano); 425-430: "How come everybody talks about the weather" (tenor, baritone, soprano, piano)
  - GSS (5), 05/07/1986; gss_342; Recording of tenor, baritone and soprano and mixed chorus with piano accompaniment; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)
    501-512: "How come everybody..." (piano, tenor, soprano, bass); 513-523: "Hallelujah" (mixed chorus)
  - GSS (6), 05/07/1986; gss_343; Recording of various performances of mixed chorus, sopranos and baritones.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 30)